Hello friends Jagdish, today's topic is today
we have another stock which
comes in the insurance sector, a few days ago we made a
stock which
is HDFC Life Insurance, you can also
check our playlist,
wherever I feel that there is an
option to make money, then I cover it
and we comment on this stock in the live market,
you can go to our Telegram and
you can see our Jagdish Stock Classes from there you can
see the stock ratio, here we
recommended this stock, I had
recommended it at 1436 and the
stock target is 15, today the stock
closed at 1457, you see the stock has
formed a good bullish green canal, it had
formed till 146, after that
even after telling, look at
some points,
I am seeing this stock breaking out on the chart today,
I will tell you what happened on this stock that
momentum came in the stock, so I want to cover
some points which I want to cover in this video,
in this video I will explain to you the levels as well as the
region  I will tell you so that by doing
such analysis you can make money
in other stocks in the coming time.
This stock had seen a spike in intraday. There was
an investor meet for them in which their
CFO
said that there is an improvement in their growth outlook.
Why is it
happening? Because their
motor premium uptake is visible. There is
demand in health insurance. The fire
segment is getting tough. All these
factors are playing towards a drive.
Their growth is improving.
Good demand has been seen in the auto sector.
The concern is that right now there is talk of second wave.
Second wave is coming in India. This is
a negative
impact. The management is quite confident that their
growth can improve. This is the
reason why you will
see that the stock momentum in intraday. If
you go and see the chart,
you can see it in the stock. On the daily chart you will see
[Music]
a stock with good volume.  It is giving a
breakout, if you see, the stock is
breaking all the previous highs and is
giving a breakout,
we captured this breakout in the live market
and we have given you this stock, this is
our Tegra channel where you
can join, we had recommended ICICI Lord here and had given a
target of 1500, so
even in intraday,
you can see that the stock is at
1468, so from the level that we had told, I
think there will be a
movement of 35 points, so we had recommended at 1436,
our recommendation was at 1436, the stock is at
1468 and we have
given a target of 1500 in the near term, if
you want to take advantage of this kind, then
you can join
[Sangeet].
You can also add our services on the front page, there are
primary services, there we
keep updating all the trending stocks with their levels, timely updates.  What happens is that
first of all we update it, it is easy to
update it, you
can do it, we will analyze how
this stock, if we
look at the fundamentals of this company stock, then the
fundamentals are also very good,
these stocks have the required skill
set for underwriting, they have a
good amount of capital which can grow its business, the
returns of this are quite
healthy, I will explain it to
you and right now the structure demand is being shown in this
structure,
any sector needs tailwinds to run,
so the tailwind is going on, right now there is
demand in the insurance sector, auto sector, pricing is increasing, if
you look at this long term, then the
returns of this company are looking quite healthy,
20% company is a top company
in its sector, it comes at B position,
we have also covered ADC Life, you
can go and see that money is being made in this too, it can be made, if we
look at the historical data of the stock, then
that is also good, the company is confident that we  If you
maintain RE at 20, the
company's earnings for the last 12 months are
also improving. This is a
good sign that the
fundamentals of the company are improving
and this impact will also be
visible on the price. If you look at the price, you will see that
if you look at any stock on a monthly basis,
you will see that the
stock had made a low in March, it had made a
hammer in it,
after that this candle
made a bullish movement,
after this the stock is moving upwards, it has
consolidated for a few months and in this month
only one day is left, 27th November,
after that there is a continuous holiday for three days,
so I think that if this
level is sustained tomorrow also, a figure will be seen in it,
this is a sign of a breakout, a multi-
month breakout is about to happen, the
stock can reach a good level from here, the bank has
also given a level of 1800 and this
level can come
in it.  I have also given a level to the level, I will take
action, you see the stock, today the daily
time frame, after a dodge, the stock has
given a confirmation that the
stock is moving upwards till it does
not move low, the stock is moving upwards, it may
cut for a few days but at some point a downtrend can come, so
in the market time, you
can trade here, you are a trader, you are an investor, you can
keep your stock tight, the investor can
remove everything and
invest, in this we have given you levels,
you can note these levels, these levels will
help you a lot in trading,
so although we had given a
level of 1500 for a few days, right now your stock has
closed at 1468, in this I think that the
upper level will be 1560, which will be
like the first target, the second target
is
1685 and the third target,
although we have given that the
stock can go up to 1560, I have become quite
optimistic, right now I am giving you three levels,
you
can reach 15 potential or you have a
very small downside.  If you don't want a stop, then you
want to work and you
want to play for a long time, if you want to play for a day, month or two months, then you can place a stop for the
95 level and according to your
system, you can place a stop or
the possible target stop plus. If you
look at its complete chart setup, you will
see that the stock
[sangeet] is
running at Rs 66 in the month,
uptake is visible in the volume,
breakout is visible in the month also,
you can see the stock in the daily, the
stock momentum is
visible at Rs 7, you can see that the Rs 7 volume is doing
well, it is
going up, it may turn or it may
show a momentum tomorrow also,
you can like and
subscribe to whichever level you like, and if you want to learn like this, then you
can do our classes, you will
see online classes, only then online classes are
technical
fundamentals and its review, so
go to our Jagdish Stock,
you should concentrate on learning once you have learnt it
You have
Lifem and after that
[music] the
good news is that you will see a join
button here also, from here you can take advantage of the join button as well,
where
in the live market also I give you some stocks,
market levels and whatever our
premium cut is, you can join in it at low cost,
here you can join,
I hope the information will be
beneficial for you and if
you do not have an account yet then you can
open a demat account and
open it, you
can take advantage of different bank accounts there, you can open a stock
account, it
is a platform, I will give you this, if you like it then
like, subscribe and
whatever your level is, you can comment and thank you very
much